<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <Glassy.Update.Title>Glassy Update Info</Glassy.Update.Title>
  
  <Glassy.Update.label>
2024/02/14(0.2.2.2):
*Definitions added in the HAR update are now supported

2023/02/13(0.2.2.1):
*Three new research studies have been added
New research enhance caravan behavior

2023/02/05(0.2.2.0):
*Added the armor added by this mod so that other BEP races can also equip it

*Added new items: tentballs and research to release tentballs

*changed the thumbnail

2023/08/08(0.2.1.0):
*Add Xenotype

*Fix CombatPower

2023/05/25(0.2.0.0):
*B.E.P Race Core is required as a prerequisite mod, and common parts have been greatly reduced.
If you are using an earlier version, various data such as hairstyles and clothes have been lost.
If you need an older version, you can download the mod before the update by going to github from the mod page.

2023/03/27(0.1.3.0):
*Fixed some graphics

*Separated FacialAnimation definitions into separate mods
To reduce the load at startup, I have separated FacialAnimation images and definitions into separate mods.
Please subscribe from the collection.

2023/03/11(0.1.2.1):
*Glassy's skills are now automatically deactivated when he leaves a faction

2023/03/05(0.1.2.0):
*Glassy now appear dressed according to their roles

2023/01/31(0.1.1.4):
*Research race restrictions have been removed

*Added new equipment
Instead of adding the equipment of another race, this mod is now added by itself
Please note that you can no longer wear clothes of other races

*Glassy who appeared at the event could not be tamed, so this has been corrected so that he can be tamed by making her a wild man when he appears

*Fixed a bug in which some clothing textures were incorrectly specified

2023/01/30(0.1.1.3):
*Various statuses are no longer corrected based on age

2023/01/29(0.1.1.2):
*Increased the number of hairstyle types to 8

2023/01/19(0.1.1.1):
*Fixed a bug that caused some backstory settings to be incorrect

2023/01/15(0.1.1.0):
*Architect categories have been merged

2023/01/08(0.1.0.4):
*The setting was changed so that the gene of Biotech's appearance system cannot be adapted

2023/01/06(0.1.0.3):
*Corrected ear layer position

*Support for the function of fertility change through Biotech linkage of HAR

2022/12/04(0.1.0.0):
*Release
</Glassy.Update.label>


</LanguageData>